

Senior Full-stack and Blockchain Developer

Tang Bao

Address: Ban Quan Lu 1201long 27hao 301shi

Birthday: June 5, 1996

Phone: (+86) 130-6375-6230

GitHub: https://github.com/Topdev0104

Skype: live:.cid.ef18a5a6e2b9dbe6

Job: Remote, Full-stack, Blockchain, Full-time, Any time zone

Front-end Developer

Full-stack Developer

Blockchain Developer

Let me introduce myself

I am a senior full-stack and blockchain developer with 5 years of strong skills and mature experience in modern software development.

I am familiar with MERN Stack and NFT ecosystem, specially NFT Minting DApps, NFT Marketplace and Staking) project.

My Main Skills

Blockchain	95%
Solidity	100%
Smart Contract	95%
NFT Ecosystem	100%
Web3.js, Ether.js	100%
Truffle, Remix, Hardhat	100%
MERN Stack	100%

Work Experience

Front-end Developer, April 2019 ~ October 2019

- Responsible for developing the UI side with React, Vue, SASS, HTML5.
- Fluent with Bootstrap versions 3-5. Regularly migrated sites to the newest version.
- Worked closely with the back-end Node developers to maintain great integration.
- Created reusable React forms/validation framework to standardize all of the forms.

Full-stack Developer, January 2020 ~ August 2020

- launched many Node websites and maintained cloud servers.
- built essential MVC projects and leveraged JavaScript, TypeScript libraries such as React, and Vue.
- collaborated with 10+ engineers to achieve innovative solutions for web products.
- developed Progressive Web App by using React, Node, Express, MongoDB, and Apache.

Blockchain Developer, November 2020 - April 2021

- Developed smart contracts for decentralized token platform on EVM.
- Developed the several NFT Minting Dapps, Marketplace and Staking project on Ethereum network.
- Developed front-end by React.js and implement smart contract integration using web3.js and ether.js

Education

Peking University

- Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc)
- July 2015 April 2019

Language

Chinese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Fluent